shiprush.com 2013-05-05

# Privacy Policy | My.ShipRush.com

Effective Date of Policy: June 1, 2009 

This document (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses the privacy practices of Z-Firm LLC (“Z-Firm”). This Privacy Policy applies to Z-Firm’s products and services including the My.ShipRush website located at my.shiprush.com (the “Website”). Please read the information below to learn what information Z-Firm collects and how it is used.   
Please keep in mind that use of Z-Firm’s products and services are governed by agreements separate from this Privacy Policy. For example, My.ShipRush is governed by its Terms of Use and the ShipRush software is governed by its user license. 

Z-Firm reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and the modifications, additions or deletions are effective immediately. You can determine if this Privacy Policy has been revised by referring to the “Effective Date of Policy” date at the top of this page. Your continued use of the Website or any other product or service of Z-Firm after such modifications constitutes your agreement to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

1.Information Collected. Z-Firm collects two types of information: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

(a)Personally Identifiable Information: 

(1)This refers to information that lets Z-Firm know the specifics about the identity of individuals. It is inherent in the services provided at the Website that Z-Firm will receive information such as the name, postal address, telephone numbers, email address, shipping information for the ecommerce transactions stored and managed by the Website (“Transaction Information”). Z-Firm will also collect information about you as part your registration and use of Z-Firm’s products and services.

(2)Z-Firm primarily uses Personally Identifiable Information to provide the requested Services. Z-Firm also may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding the products and services offered by Z-Firm and shipping related products and services offered by Z-Firm’s partners. The Personally Identifiable Information may also be used to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce any agreements with Z-Firm including, without limitation, the Website’s Terms of Use and this Private Policy.

(3)In the event a shipping carrier or other Z-Firm partner (such as an ecommerce platform) is investigating or enforcing a breach or violation of its policies, procedures or user agreements, Z-Firm may share Personally Identifiable Information with the affected partner to allow the partner to conduct its investigation or address the actual or alleged problem, issue or concern.

(b)Non-Personally Identifiable Information: 

(1)This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. Z-Firm may gather certain information about you based on your use of the Website. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. Examples of the kind of information that may be collected include the uniform resource identifier (“URI”) for the internet site that you just came from, the URI for internet site you go to next, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. The Website also may store cookies on your computer. 

(2)A cookie is a small text file used to store information (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify information about you. A URI is the name of a resource on the internet. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a network such as the internet. So, an IP address is assigned to your computer whenever you are using the internet and allows other computers on the internet to locate and identify your computer. 

(3)Z-Firm may also collect, either directly or through a third party service (e.g. Google Analytics), certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. In general, Z-Firm uses this information to learn where visitors to the Website come from, how they interact with the Website and to generate reports about the use and interaction with the Website. The goal is to improve the quality of the Website and to increase the effectiveness of Z-Firm’s marketing initiatives. 

2.How Information is Shared or Transferred.

(a)Z-Firm may provide Transaction Information to shipping carriers. However, such information has typically already been provided to such shipping carrier in connection with a prior shipping transaction. Other than the shipping carriers, Z-Firm does not sell, trade, or rent Transaction Information to others as part of its normal business operations.

(b)Z-Firm may provide Personally Identifiable Information to third parties who provide services for the benefit of Z-Firm or Z-Firm believes, in its sole discretion, will be useful or applicable to you or your business (collectively “Business Associates”). The use of your Personally Identifiable Information by these Business Associates is restricted to using the information on behalf of Z-Firm or as otherwise directed by Z-Firm.

(c)Z-Firm reserves the right to transfer any and all information that it collects to third parties, in the event of a sale, merger or transfer by Z-Firm of all or any portion of its assets business.

(d)Z-Firm also will disclose information as required by law enforcement or judicial authorities, on receipt of a court order or subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. Z-Firm reserves the right to report to law enforcement any activities that it, in good faith, believes to be unlawful.

3.Updating Information. Account information provided during registration for a product or service becomes part of Z-Firm’s business records and cannot be deleted or changed. Without limiting the prior sentence, the Website does provide a feature for a user to update account information. Z-Firm may retain past information because some residual information will be part of other business records such as computer storage backups.

4.Third Party Privacy Policies and Data Collection. This document only addresses the collection, use and disclosure of information by Z-Firm and does not cover third party practices. For example, shipping carriers and ecommerce platforms each have their own user agreements, practices as to the collection, use and disclosure of data, and policies governing the privacy aspects of that data. Z-Firm is not responsible for the policies or practices of any third party.

5.Children Under 13. This website is directed to adults and is not directed to children under the age of 13. Z-Firm does not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13.

6.Additional Information. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Z-Firm:  
Z-Firm LLC  
Attn: Customer Service  
120 Lakeside Avenue, Suite 101  
Seattle, WA 98122  
Email: info@zfirmllc.com
